

MAX BODELIER

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

https://resume.maxbodelier.com/

m.a.j.bodelier@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/max-bodelier

WHO AM I?

I have over two years of experience in software development in different industries. I am an excellent and enthusiastic team player and show perseverance regarding my tasks. Strong social and communication skills are at the core of my competences. I always aim to achieve the best possible results for the customer in the most efficient way.

PROFILE

- Master in Innovation Sciences University of Technology Eindhoven
- ± 29 December 1993
- Dutch (mother tongue), English (fluent), German (basic)

HIGHLIGHTS

CAREER

Mediaan (2019 - present)
Junior software engineer
Software engineer within development team

Mediaan (2017 - 2018)
Junior management consultant
Management consultant data science within
public healthcare industry

EXPERIENCE

- Software Engineer
- Management Consultant

HIGHLIGHTS

SKILLS

- Working Agile (Scrum)
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Sass/Less
- VueJS
- Amazone Web Services
- Contentful Headless CMS
- Entry level Microsoft Azure
- Entry level C#
- Entry level .NET Core
- Google Tag Manager
- Entry Level Google Analytics

HIGHLIGHTS MARKETS

- Digital Signage Services
- Healthcare Insurance
- Public Healthcare

SNAPSHOT

PROJECTS

SCALA, SITTARD

Scala focusses on building strategic partnerships with the world's leading brands to apply a wide array of technology — including digital signs, mobile sensors, audience intelligence, virtual reality, and computer vision technology — in the physical space. They are transforming how consumers experience retail stores, quick-service restaurants, airports, banks, and corporate environments with a "marketing first" point of view, matching the vision with the strategy, experience, and delivery capability to make the client's project a success.

MARKETING, DIGITAL SIGNAGE

2020 - Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Design and implementation of various front ends (websites) for each of the Stratacache company brands. Moving from separate WordPress CMS instances towards a unifying bespoke platform (VueJS), with a headless CMS (Contentful) to back it up. By unifying content, Scala and Stratacache have single place to maintain and update content from a single hub and structuring it so it can be used in any digital channel, it is currently setup to handle and distribute content to eighteen websites from a centralized system, with over half a million of page visits per month.

AEVITAE, HEERLEN

Aevitae is a leading authorized agent in the Netherlands specialized in servicing healthcare, employee benefit and personal benefit insurance on behalf of insurers. Aevitae has a customer base of more than 250.000.

A INSURANCE

2019 - 2019

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Implementation of .NET Core backend system which implements business rules for checking incoming health declarations on their validity and avoid wrongful payment to the insured. The main flow the application included: queueing incoming messages (Azure service bus), process these messages by checking their validity against the predefined business rules (.NET Core, C#), and lastly output the results to a dashboard for the auditing department.

MEANDERGROEP ZUID-LIMBURG, HEERLEN

MeanderGroep Zuid-Limburg is a public Healthcare provider for all age categories. They assist in the areas of prevention, wellbeing, living, care, and ease of life. The want to give their patients control over their own life and live as independent as possible. They achieve this by implementing innovative initiatives and use these to deliver the highest quality of care to their patients.

A HEALTHCARE

2017 - 2019

© DATA SCIENCE/MANAGEMENT CONSULTANT

Enabling/implementing data science solutions for MeanderGroep, where the delivery of healthcare to patients and Backoffice processes could benefit from. Activities included: researching the needs/opportunities within the organization where innovative data science solutions could be realized, creating an overview (organization wide) to show all possibilities for data science solutions for management, define business cases for problem owners for implementing the data science solutions, manage the realization/implementation of data science business cases.

OVERVIEW

TRAINING

MICROSOFT CERTIFICATION PROGRAM, 2018

I have participated in several Microsoft certification programs as part of my personal development. These programs where provided by a one-on-one teacher on location in Goa, India, where I have travelled to. These programs where provided by Koenig Solutions. The courses in which I have participated are given below.

- 20480C PROGRAMMING IN HTML5 WITH JAVASCRIPT AND CSS3
- 20487D DEVELOPING MICROSOFT AZURE AND WEB SERVICES.
- 20486D DEVELOPING ASP.NET CORE MVC WEBAPPLICATIONS